<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Paul Grave</title><link>https://paulgrav.github.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Paul Grave</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 18:02:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://paulgrav.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>An iOS Shortcut for Feedbin’s read-it-later service</title><link>https://paulgrav.github.io/posts/feedbin/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 18:02:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://paulgrav.github.io/posts/feedbin/</guid><description>Get the Shortcut here
Over the years I’ve used multiple read-it-later services on my iOS devices. From Instapaper, Pocket, and Apple’s own Reading List and for various reasons none of them has stuck with me. There has always been something that I’ve not quite liked about those services.
Fast forward to 2020 and I think I finally found the ideal solution. It avoids running additional apps, and it’s free (sort of).</description></item><item><title>Helloworld</title><link>https://paulgrav.github.io/posts/helloworld/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Nov 2020 21:12:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://paulgrav.github.io/posts/helloworld/</guid><description>Hello World</description></item><item><title>Push notifications from your wired Doorbell</title><link>https://paulgrav.github.io/posts/doorbell/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Nov 2020 09:41:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://paulgrav.github.io/posts/doorbell/</guid><description>Doorbell Push Notifications on iOS First, caveats and disclaimers.
You’re going to need to be comfortable with wiring and running software on UNIX-based platforms. N.B. I’d advise you to find a qualified electrician to do the wiring. I don’t want to hear about anyone electrocuting themselves whilst attempting this at home.
My solution is focused on iOS and UNIX. That’s what I know, and that’s what I have. It’s possible that it could be tweaked to work on Android and Windows but I have access to neither of those platforms.</description></item><item><title>Using Cloudflare Access to secure access to service on your home network</title><link>https://paulgrav.github.io/posts/cloudflareaccess/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Nov 2020 09:40:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://paulgrav.github.io/posts/cloudflareaccess/</guid><description>Using Cloudflare Access to secure access to services on your home network The problem I’ve always wanted to run services on my local network and access them remotely but until now setting up authorization and encryption has been a minefield. Certificates would cost money, and the setup was a pain. Authorization would need to be configured on an per-app basis. Apps may have built-in auth, or they may leave that problem to the user.</description></item></channel></rss>